Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Chrysler Corp. UAW - discharge of Leo J. Busch, 1943-1947 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Chrysler Corp. UAW - discharge of Wisom Safford, 1943-1947 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Chrysler Corp. UAW - protesting daily record and penalty of one week layoff for Herva Smith and Benjamin Madison, 1943- 1947 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Chrysler Corp. UAW - reimbursing T. Hopkins, 1943-1947 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Chrysler Corp. UAW - unjust penalization of Paul Sabo, 1943-1947 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Chrysler Corp., UAW - discharge of H. Riley, 1943-1944 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Chrysler Corp., UAW - discharge of John Busiettel, 1943-1944 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Chrysler Corp., UAW - discharge of John Mackay, 1943-1944 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Chrysler Corp., UAW - discharge of Solomon Deutsch, 1943-1944 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Chrysler Corp., UAW - disciplinary action against F. Barrus, 1943-1944 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Warner Gear Div., Borg Warner Corp. and Local No. 287 UAW, 1944; Publication (Box 74, Folder 4)
    Notes: Arbitration award
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Implications of automation, Publication (Box 74, Folder 5)
    Author: James Stern
  - Item 2: Possible effects of automation on older workers, Publication (Box 74, Folder 5)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: How do we stand on the pension plan?, 1947; Publication (Box 74, Folder 6)
    Notes: Newspaper clipping
  - Item 2: Leadership Studies Center - Group Insurance Bargaining, 1966; Publication (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Outline of retirement plan, 1947; Publication (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Prepaid Psychiatric Care Experience with UAW members, 1969; Publication (Box 74, Folder 6)
    Author: Melvin A. Glasser
  - Item 5: correspondence from International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1948; Publication (Box 74, Folder 6)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Health and insurance welfare program for members and their families of Local 259, 1948; Publication (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: A Glossary of terms used in arbitration and/or negotiations -, Publication (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: A real handful, Kaiser-Frazer - UAW-CIO, Social Security Program, 1961; Publication (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Houdaille-Hershey Corporation and the UAW-CIO, Pension Plan for hourly-rated employees, July 26, 1950, Publication (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Leadership Studies Center - Group Insurance Bargaining, Publication (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: The UAW's First Retirement Plan, dated September 28, 1949., Publication (Box 74, Folder 7)
    Notes: Copy of original
  - Item 7: UAW Legal Services Plan -, 1977; Publication (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: UAW legal services plan, including trust and related agreements, 1977; Publication (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Ford Motor Company and UAW-CIO retirement plan: effective March 1, 1950, with amendments effective October 1, 1950-, 1952; Publication (Box 74, Folder 7)
    Author: Ford Motor Company
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Attend your local union meeting, Publication (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Attend your union meetings, Publication (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: If you must beat your gums, Publication (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: It's in your hands, Publication (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: It's just good business to join the UAW-CIO, Publication (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Most farm children become city workers, Publication (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Neighbors and friends, Publication (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Start it right, Publication (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: The UAW is more than a union, Publication (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: UAW-CIO gives leadership to the American Labor Movement, Publication (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Who writes your contract, Publication (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: You are invited to board, Publication (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: Labor looks at labor: some members of the United Auto Workers undertake a self-examination., 1963; Publication (Box 74, Folder 8)
    Author: Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Michigan Legislative Guide (1975-1976) (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Protecting you and your family, 1968; Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: The record shows vote the Humphrey-Muskie ticket, 1968; Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: The record shows, 1968; Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: UAW local union cap and Legislative Committee handbook, 1969; Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Why are your taxes too high?, 1968; Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Would you trust the republicans? They took away SUB before, 1968; Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: UAW: a new beginning for a better tomorrow, a set of facts on which to build a new public policy in 1977, Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: UAW-CAP Michigan legislative program '77, 1977; Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Community Action Program
  - Item 10: Collective Bargaining Handbook for workers security programs, 1949; Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Labor's stake in employment and retirement, Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Supplementary security programs under collective bargaining, Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: The food - UAW-CIO workers security program plans, Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: The hospital service labor wants - a formula for progress, Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Unions move into supplementary security programs under collective bargaining, Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Correspondence and memos, Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Summation of UAW-CIO 1949 demands for workers security: letter of transmittal to the Chrysler Corporation... (Pensions and health security)..., Publication (Box 75, Folder 1)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Chrysler Dept.
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: A call to action, health care for all Americans, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: A legislative program for retired workers, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Alcohol and drug abuse recovery program, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Alcoholism and drug abuse in the work place, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Community Services Program, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Facts about drugs, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Food stamps make the difference, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Help unemployed members with food stamps, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: How to organize and meet the needs of our UAW..., Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: How to organize and meet the needs, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: How we can be helpful...on mortgages, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: How we can be helpfulon mortgages, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Preparing for a disaster, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: To improve the quality of life, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Toward a profile of your community facts for action, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Toward Welfare Reform, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Urban coalitions, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Welfare in Michigan, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Welfare tell it like it is!, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: Who is on welfare?, Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: Slowdown taking spotlight which sit-down once held, 1939; Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: UAW-Chrysler Newsgram, 1988; Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1988 may
  - Item 23: What Editors Say, 1939; Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1939 November 2
  - Item 24: Correspondence, 1939; Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Item 25: Press releases, 1939; Publication (Box 75, Folder 2)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Fluid drives and brass knuckles: Chrysler labor policies, obsolete as hand cranks, 1947; Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Author: Norman Matthews
  - Item 2: Press releases from Chrysler, 1945; Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Press releases from Chrysler, 1948; Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Competitive shop organizer, 1946; Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.1:no.1-2 (1946)
  - Item 5: Competitive shop organizer, 1947; Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.2:no.1-6 (1947)
  - Item 6: Correspondence, Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Bylaws International Chrysler Council UAW, 1969; Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: More comment by editors on the Chrysler 'slow-down' strike, 1939; Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Notes: 1939 November 17
  - Item 9: The 1967 auto negotiations and the needs of the U.S. economy, National Chrysler Dept., Publication (Box 75, Folder 3)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: As citizens we pledge ourselves - pamphlet - local info, 1960; Publication (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Con Con, Michigan's constitution; a look at the record, analysis and comparison, 1962; Publication (Box 75, Folder 4)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Citizenship Dept.
  - Item 3: Subsidies are fire engines, Publication (Box 75, Folder 4)
    Author: Christina Malman
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Washington Report, 1963; Publication (Box 75, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.3:no.36 (1963)
  - Item 2: Washington Report, 1964; Publication (Box 75, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.4:no.1-4,7-25,27-45,48-51 (1964)
  - Item 3: Washington Report, 1964; Publication (Box 75, Folder 5)
    Notes: Special issue
  - Item 4: United Automobile Workers v. Hoosier Corp., 1966; Publication (Box 75, Folder 5)
    Notes: Court case
  - Item 5: United States District Court Eastern District of Michigan Southern Division: United States of America v. International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW-CIO), brief in support of defendant's motion to d, Publication (Box 75, Folder 5)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: In the spirit of '37 - An economic program for the auto workers, 1937; Publication (Box 75, Folder 6)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: UAW sets up own book club, first union one, 1941; Publication (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: The gas-engine union, 1944; Publication (Box 75, Folder 7)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Can you answer the $50,000 question?, Publication (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Driverless tractors: the latest thing in mechanized farming, Publication (Box 75, Folder 8)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Michigan Legislative Guide (1975-1976) (Box 75.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Protecting you and your family, 1968; Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: The record shows vote the Humphrey-Muskie ticket, 1968; Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: The record shows, 1968; Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: UAW local union cap and Legislative Committee handbook, 1969; Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Why are your taxes too high?, 1968; Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Would you trust the republicans? They took away SUB before, 1968; Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: UAW: a new beginning for a better tomorrow, a set of facts on which to build a new public policy in 1977, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: UAW-CAP Michigan legislative program '77, 1977; Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 1)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: A call to action, health care for all Americans, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: A legislative program for retired workers, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Alcohol and drug abuse recovery program, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Alcoholism and drug abuse in the work place, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Community Services Program, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Facts about drugs, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Food stamps make the difference, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Help unemployed members with food stamps, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: How to organize and meet the needs of our UAW..., Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: How to organize and meet the needs, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: How we can be helpful...on mortgages, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: How we can be helpfulon mortgages, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Preparing for a disaster, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: To improve the quality of life, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Toward a profile of your community facts for action, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Toward Welfare Reform, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Urban coalitions, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Welfare in Michigan, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: Welfare tell it like it is!, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: Who is on welfare?, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 2)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Competitive shop organizer, 1946; Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Competitive shop organizer, 1947; Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Correspondence, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 3)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Subsidies are fire engines, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 4)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: United Automobile Workers v. Hoosier Corp., 1966; Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: United States District Court Eastern District of Michigan Southern Division: United States of America v. International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW-CIO), brief in support of defendant's motion to d, Publication (Box 75.1, Folder 5)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Die Casters News Letter, 1951; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: Oct.,Dec. 1951
  - Item 2: Die Casters News Letter, 1952; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: Jan.-Apr., July-Aug., Nov.- Dec. 1952
  - Item 3: Die Casters News Letter, 1953; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: Feb.-Mar., May-June, Aug.- Sept., Nov.-Dec. 1953
  - Item 4: Die Casters News Letter, 1954; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: Apr.-May, July, Sept.-Oct., Dec. 1954
  - Item 5: Die Casters News Letter, 1955; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: Feb.-Mar., June-July, Sept.- Oct., Dec. 1955
  - Item 6: Die Casters News Letter, 1956; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: Feb., Apr., June, Aug., Nov.-Dec. 1956
  - Item 7: Die Casters News Letter, 1957; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: Feb., May, July-Sept., Nov.- Dec. 1957
  - Item 8: Die Casters News Letter, 1958; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: Jan. 1958
  - Item 9: Die Casting Newsletter, 1949; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.1, no.2-9 (1949)
  - Item 10: Die Casting Newsletter, 1950; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.1, no.10-15, 18-19 (1950)
  - Item 11: Die Casting Newsletter, 1951; Publication (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Notes: vol.1, no.20-21,23 (1951)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Aviation Industry economics, 1940; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Education Dept.
  - Item 2: The Elements of trade unionism: simple answers to simple questions, 1937; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Address by Merlin D. Bishop, 1937; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Author: Merlin D. Bishop
  - Item 4: Are you just half a man?, 1932; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Duties of the shop steward, 1937; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Friday the thirteenth, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Author: Alex McGowan
    Notes: Script for play
  - Item 7: Social Action, 1937; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.3:no.4 (1937:Feb.)
  - Item 8: The Assembler, 1949; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol.9:no.16-19
  - Item 9: The Economics of the Automobile Industry, part four, 1940; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: The General Motors Corporation, What is it? How big is it? Who owns it? And all about it, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Victory, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Notes: Booklet of news clippings
  - Item 12: Exhibit 19: what workers thought of the auto industry 20 years ago: from an official U.S. government report to President Franklin D. Roosevelt "On regularizing employment and improvement of labor conditions in the automobile industry", January 23, 1935., 1955; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile Workers of America (A.F. of L.)
  - Item 13: How to organize a cooperative in your community, Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Industrial unionism in the American labor movement, 1937; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Author: Theresa Wolfson
  - Item 15: Occupational disease and workmen's compensation, 1937; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Medical Advisory Board and Education Department.
  - Item 16: Security, UAW-CIO: the road to a free conscience and a full life, 1946; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: The principles of unionism: questions and answers., 1938; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: What organized labor wants: a popular description of trade union philosophy, economics and ideals, 1937; Publication (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Author: August Claessens
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: No bottleneck in aviation: a plan to rationalize the labor supply for the aviation industry, 1941; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Author: Frankensteen, Richard T.
  - Item 2: 500 planes a day, a program for the utilization of the automobile industry for mass production of defense planes, 1941; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Apprenticeship and the UAW-CIO, 1941; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America.
  - Item 4: Article - untitled from the Education Dept., 1941; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Close harmony: a voice and vote for every member in the UAW-CIO regardless of race, color, or creed., 1941; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: General Motors: an industrial empire, 1941; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Housing for defense, 1941; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Author: R. J. Thomas
  - Item 8: How to conduct a union meeting, 1941; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: How to win for the union: a discussion for U.A.W. Stewards and Committeemen, 1941; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: It's your union, brother!, 1941; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Putting the world on wheels: a brief picture of the rise of the auto industry, including many pertinent economic facts of interest to UAW-CIO members, 1941; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: The answer is yes the auto industry is making money, 1941; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: UAW-CIO, the American way: the Spirit of '76 is the spirit of the CIO., 1941; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Wife in step, 1941; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: You and the draft; what you should know about it: deferments, classification, appeals, financial relief., 1941; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: You have won these gains: make sure you keep them!, 1940; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: You want unity!, 1941; Publication (Box 76, Folder 3)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: List of schools and subjects in Detroit Area, 1941; Publication (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: The Distributor, 1941; Publication (Box 76, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.2:no.7 (1941)
  - Item 3: UAW-CIO Education bulletin, 1941; Publication (Box 76, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol.11:no.1-4 (1941)
  - Item 4: Correspondence and news articles, Publication (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: The 1941-1942 UAW-CIO educational program mandate, Publication (Box 76, Folder 4)
- UAW (United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, aka United Auto Workers), Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: It's your fight! Buy U.S. defense bonds, Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Want a new home?, Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Beware of witch-hunts, 1942; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: How to conduct a union meeting, 1941; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: How to organize education in your local union: a short handbook for UAW-CIO Education Chairmen and Committeemen of UAW-CIO Education Committees, 1942; Publication (Box 77, Folder 1)